var questions = [{
	"question": "50 + 71  = ?",
	"option1": "131",
	"option2": "121",
	"option3": "126",
	"option4": "Semua jawaban benar",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "132 + 81 = ?",
	"option1": "213",
	"option2": "441",
	"option3": "211",
	"option4": "210",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "213 - 125",
	"option1": "92",
	"option2": "78",
	"option3": "101",
	"option4": "88",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "113 x 4 = ?",
	"option1": "452",
	"option2": "446",
	"option3": "451",
	"option4": "999",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "24 : 6 = ?",
	"option1": "3",
	"option2": "2",
	"option3": "7",
	"option4": "4",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "3 x 3 x 3 = ?",
	"option1": "9",
	"option2": "27",
	"option3": "56",
	"option4": "18",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "441 - 115 = ?",
	"option1": "333",
	"option2": "326",
	"option3": "321",
	"option4": "345",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "46 x 2 = ?",
	"option1": "92",
	"option2": "72",
	"option3": "112",
	"option4": "83",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "26 x 26 = ?",
	"option1": "676",
	"option2": "576",
	"option3": "598",
	"option4": "666",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "100 : 5 : 5 = ?",
	"option1": "6",
	"option2": "20",
	"option3": "25",
	"option4": "Tidak ada jawaban yang benar",
	"answer": "4"
}];